[
    {
        "QuestionNum": "1",
        "Question": "Who is the actor who plays MacGyver?",
        "A": "Bruce McGill",
        "B": "Dana Elcar",
        "C": "Richard Dean Anderson",
        "D": "Michael Des Barres",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "2",
        "Question": "What is MacGyver's grandfathers's name?",
        "A": "Harry Jackson",
        "B": "Guy Roberts",
        "C": "Jesse Colton",
        "D": "Peter Thornton",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "3",
        "Question": "Who is the voodoo priestess in MacGyver?",
        "A": "Nikki Carpenter",
        "B": "Lisa Woodman",
        "C": "Penny Parker",
        "D": "Mama Lorain",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "4",
        "Question": "Who are the three Colton brothers?",
        "A": "Frank, Jesse, Perry",
        "B": "Billy, Frank, Jesse",
        "C": "Tim, Billy, Irwin",
        "D": "Jesse, Perry, Tim",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "5",
        "Question": "What is the name of the Colton family dog?",
        "A": "Frog",
        "B": "Dog",
        "C": "Buddy",
        "D": "Abe",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "6",
        "Question": "Who was MacGyver's friend who died while trying to defuse a bomb at sea?",
        "A": "Robert Sanborn",
        "B": "Larry Whitecloud",
        "C": "Charlie Robinson",
        "D": "Darin Cooper",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "7",
        "Question": "What is the name of MacGyver's son?",
        "A": "Tim Wexler",
        "B": "Caspar Kasabian",
        "C": "Henry Jones",
        "D": "Sean Malloy",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "8",
        "Question": "How many seasons did MacGyver have?",
        "A": "6",
        "B": "7",
        "C": "8",
        "D": "9",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "9",
        "Question": "How can you tell when Jack Dalton is 'stretching the truth'?",
        "A": "He laughs",
        "B": "He doesn't make eye contact",
        "C": "His eye twitches",
        "D": "He wrings his hands",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "10",
        "Question": "MacGyver works for two companies throughout the series. What is the second company?",
        "A": "Spy Center Inc.",
        "B": "Department of External Services",
        "C": "Central Intelligence Agency",
        "D": "Phoenix Foundation",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "11",
        "Question": "Based on the previous question, which company did he first work at?",
        "A": "Department of External Services",
        "B": "Central Intelligence Agency",
        "C": "Phoenix Foundation",
        "D": "Spy Center Inc.",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "12",
        "Question": "Where does MacGyver meet Penny Parker?",
        "A": "Restaurant",
        "B": "Airport",
        "C": "Bank",
        "D": "Grocery Store",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "13",
        "Question": "Who is MacGyver's greatest foe?",
        "A": "Matlock",
        "B": "Brandenberg",
        "C": "Malcolm",
        "D": "Murdoc",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "14",
        "Question": "What is MacGyver's favorite sport?",
        "A": "Soccer",
        "B": "Football",
        "C": "Hockey",
        "D": "Baseball",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "15",
        "Question": "Why didn't MacGyver like guns?",
        "A": "They are too loud",
        "B": "He never grew up around them",
        "C": "Childhood incident",
        "D": "He actually loved them",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "16",
        "Question": "In the episode 'Two Times Trouble,' Carla impersonates her twin sister. Who is this?",
        "A": "Roxanne",
        "B": "Judy",
        "C": "Michelle",
        "D": "Charity",
        "Answer": "A"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "17",
        "Question": "Who runs the Challenger's club alongside his wife, Cynthia?",
        "A": "Larry",
        "B": "Booker",
        "C": "Andrew",
        "D": "Robert",
        "Answer": "B"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "18",
        "Question": "What is the name of the restaurant that MacGyver helps Earl Dent get a job at?",
        "A": "Los Polos Hermanos",
        "B": "Mr. Cluck's Chicken Shack",
        "C": "Cluckin' Bell",
        "D": "Chicken Habit",
        "Answer": "D"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "19",
        "Question": "Who tried teaching MacGyver a 'lesson in evil'?",
        "A": "Murdoc",
        "B": "Deborah",
        "C": "Zito",
        "D": "Nicolai Kossov",
        "Answer": "C"
    },
    {
        "QuestionNum": "20",
        "Question": "What is MacGyver's first name?",
        "A": "Angus",
        "B": "Harry",
        "C": "Dexter",
        "D": "Craig",
        "Answer": "A"
    }
]